<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>anton</title>
    <description>A small growth today makes progression happen...</description>
    <link>www.anton23.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="www.anton23.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2014 23:03:10 -0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2014 23:03:10 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.1.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Impostor Syndrome</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;A programmer friend of mine sent me a presentation by  Julie Pagano on Impostor Syndrome.  I believe it’s a highly important subject in the coding world (or any world actually).  Below is a link to the video, and the takeaways…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;impostor-syndrome&quot;&gt;Impostor Syndrome&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“A psychological phenomenon in  which people are unable to internalize their accomplishments.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;To an average person, there’s equilibrium in seeing failures and successes.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;To someone who suffers from Impostor Syndrome, “victories diminish in importance; failures loom large.”
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;I was just lucky&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;I’m not that smart&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;I’m not a good programmer&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;I’m a FRAUD&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Those with Impostor Syndrome hold themselves back, do not share knowledge (because of feeling inadequate), avoid collaboration, don’t help with open-source, and don’t apply for jobs.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Those with Impostor Syndrome: “Start small. Remain small.  End up small.”&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Some people with Impostor Syndrome go to other end and feel pressured to play catch-up where they &lt;strong&gt;push themselves too hard&lt;/strong&gt; – upto burnout.  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;burnout&quot;&gt;Burnout&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Long-term exhaustion and diminished interest in work.”  People with burntout makes it hard to come back sometimes – game over.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;dunning-kruger-effect&quot;&gt;Dunning-Kruger Effect&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“A cognitive bias in which unskilled individuals suffer from illusory superiority, mistakenly rating their ability much higher than average.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;solutions&quot;&gt;Solutions?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Build a Party
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;People whom you could trust for feedback&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;You’re going to have bad days, and this party should provide support&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Track Measurable Progress
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Have an objective data for you to assess yourself.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Setting practical and achievable goals.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Train Yourself to Look for Positives
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Making a Habit (e.g., once a day?)&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Help others find positives&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Avoid Negatives
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Avoid “that person” (e.g., nasty person).  They’re invalid source of data.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Avoid creating negative space in the world
        &lt;ul&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;No feigning surprise&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;No &lt;em&gt;“well… actually”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;No backseat driving&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Help Others
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;It gives you a different perspective on things you don’t expect.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Kill Your Heroes
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;See the human being.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;480&quot; height=&quot;360&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;youtube-player&quot; src=&quot;//www.youtube.com/embed/1i8ylq4j_EY?wmode=transparent&amp;amp;amp;autoplay=0&amp;amp;amp;rel=0&amp;amp;amp;showinfo=0&amp;amp;amp;autohide=1&amp;amp;amp;color=white&amp;amp;amp;&quot; type=&quot;text/html&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2014 07:43:58 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>www.anton23.com/skill/life/2014/09/30/impostor/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">www.anton23.com/skill/life/2014/09/30/impostor/</guid>
        
        
        <category>skill</category>
        
        <category>life</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>September Squatz 2</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;assessing-data-objectively&quot;&gt;Assessing Data Objectively&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last year September, my squats was 205x4.  This September of this year it’s 245x3.  It may appear like a 40 pound increase over the 12 months.  However, there are a few important distinctions:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;In the 2013 video, I was doing a high-bar squat.  In the data below, I switched from low-bar squat to ATG squat.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;In 2013, my 1repmax was 235 lbs.  In the past 12 months, the highest I had was 273 lbs. (1repmax provides a more accurate comparison between lifts)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conclusion, looking at the data, there was about a 40-pound increase in my squats.  I’m not sure if this is an average increase (I’m gonna ask the interwebz), but definitely it’s progress!  My goal for the next 12 months is to keep the increase around 40 lbs if possible.  (Unfortunately, I’m currently nursing a hip flexor injury which already has me on a slow start.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/KWC64e5.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/oUA3iv6.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;&lt;iframe width=&quot;360&quot; height=&quot;480&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;youtube-player&quot; src=&quot;//www.youtube.com/embed/8e_qFHtg2os?wmode=transparent&amp;amp;amp;autoplay=0&amp;amp;amp;rel=0&amp;amp;amp;showinfo=0&amp;amp;amp;autohide=1&amp;amp;amp;color=white&amp;amp;amp;&quot; type=&quot;text/html&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
  &lt;figcaption&gt;2013 September Squatz (205x4)&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;&lt;iframe width=&quot;360&quot; height=&quot;480&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;youtube-player&quot; src=&quot;//www.youtube.com/embed/jzT3osdYQ_A?wmode=transparent&amp;amp;amp;autoplay=0&amp;amp;amp;rel=0&amp;amp;amp;showinfo=0&amp;amp;amp;autohide=1&amp;amp;amp;color=white&amp;amp;amp;&quot; type=&quot;text/html&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
  &lt;figcaption&gt;2014 September Squatz (245x3)&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2014 07:40:58 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>www.anton23.com/exercise/2014/09/30/september-squatz-2/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">www.anton23.com/exercise/2014/09/30/september-squatz-2/</guid>
        
        
        <category>exercise</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Angular.js</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;example-of-minimum-set-up-for-angular&quot;&gt;Example of minimum set-up for Angular&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;index.html.haml&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;!!! 5
%html{&quot;ng-app&quot;=&amp;gt;&quot;gemStore&quot;}
  %head
    / $BOOTSTRAP  CSS CDN 
    %link(rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;  href=&#39;//netdna.bootstrapcdn.com/bootstrap/3.1.1/css/bootstrap.min.css&#39;)

    / Stylesheets
    = stylesheet_link_tag &#39;custom&#39;

  %body{&quot;ng-controller&quot;=&amp;gt;&quot;StoreController as store&quot;}
    .container
      .product.row{&quot;ng-hide&quot; =&amp;gt; &quot;store.product.soldOut&quot;}
        %h3
          {{store.product.name}}
          %em.pull-right ${{store.product.price}}
        %button{&quot;ng-show&quot; =&amp;gt; &quot;store.product.canPurchase&quot;} Add to Cart


    / JQUERY CDN
    = javascript_include_tag  &quot;//ajax.googleapis.com/ajax/libs/jquery/2.1.0/jquery.min.js&quot;

    / AngularJS
    = javascript_include_tag &quot;//ajax.googleapis.com/ajax/libs/angularjs/1.2.25/angular.min.js&quot;

    / Javascripts
    = javascript_include_tag &quot;app.js&quot;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;app.js&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;(function() {
  var app = angular.module(&#39;gemStore&#39;, []);

  app.controller(&#39;StoreController&#39;, function(){
    this.product = gem;
  });

  var gem = {
    name: &#39;Azurite&#39;,
    price: 110.50,
    canPurchase: true,
    soldOut: false
  };
})();
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2014 07:43:58 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>www.anton23.com/skill/2014/09/24/angular/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">www.anton23.com/skill/2014/09/24/angular/</guid>
        
        
        <category>skill</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cognitive Behavior Therapy</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;feelings&quot;&gt;Feelings&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;why-do-you-feel-the-way-you-do&quot;&gt;Why do you feel the way you do?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to Cognitive Behaviour Therapy, people feel emotionally bad for three reasons:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They have a negative view of themselves as people;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They interpret experiences in a negative and biased way; and&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They have a negative view of the future – they expect everything to continue the way it is.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If this is true, this might also mean that happy people feel happy for the following reasons:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They have a positive view of themselves as people;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They interpret experiences in a positive and unbiased (or even positively biased) way; and&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They have a positive view of the future, they expect everything to continue the way it is.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;identifying-negative-thoughts-in-people&quot;&gt;Identifying Negative Thoughts in People.&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do they…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Have a negative view of themselves as people?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Have a negative biased view of situations?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Feel negatively about the future?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;why-think-that-way-if-it-is-so-self-defeating&quot;&gt;Why think that way if it is so self-defeating?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most depressed or anxious people do not like feeling unhappy, depressed or anxious. However, having a negative view of oneself, of the situation and of the future can become a habit. Depression or vulnerability to depression may come from too many years of holding wrong views of oneself as weak or unlovable, thinking in negative or biased ways, and knowing (or thinking one knows) that problems will continue in the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;am-i-to-blame-if-i-feel-bad&quot;&gt;Am I to blame if I feel bad?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No, not at all! Many factors contribute to feeling depressed and anxious. It is suggested that you might be able to protect yourself from some of these feelings by taking positive action to improve your thinking patterns and thereby changing your life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;what-is-lack-of-sadness-or-anxiety-related-to&quot;&gt;What is lack of sadness or anxiety related to?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The good news is that you can be happy, even if you are as poor as the next person and you don’t have wonderful possessions, glamorous looks, fabulous clothes, a great job, icons and successes etc. The bad news is that you might need to work at developing skills which protect you against feeling depressed and anxious.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;wutiwuf&quot;&gt;WUTIWUF&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Changing your view about yourself, changing your thoughts about events and changing your view of the future will change the way you feel. This is a really simple idea but highly effective. Cognitive Therapy maintains that your emotions are strongly influenced by what you think. Negative emotions are caused by thinking negative (or warped) thoughts. Positive emotions are caused by thinking positive (or unwarped) thoughts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What you think is what you feel is not a new strategy. Shakespeare, for example, gave Hamlet the following lines “There is neither good nor ill but thinking makes it so”. Here he recognised that it is one’s interpretations of events rather than the quality of the event that determines their emotional impact.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;exercises&quot;&gt;EXERCISES:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1UxoDyqfTBL6QPys_IkFk7XiGZnmWBVcloM6b1aFtGLU/edit#gid=0&quot;&gt;Auto Talk Quiz and Bad Hair Day&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;do-the-same-thoughts-result-in-the-same-feelings&quot;&gt;Do the same thoughts result in the same feelings?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As you probably noticed by now, different feelings are often produced by different types of thoughts. For example, misery and depression usually arise from internal criticism (I’m hopeless, useless, unlovable, etc).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anger is often produced by thinking that external situations should be better. For example, the world should work differently, life should be fairer, I should not be misjudged, it is not reasonable, they should understand my point of view, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anger is often only displayed where the person feels in a powerful position or at least in an equal position. For example, parents often get angry with children…people are reticent to get too grumpy at their boss (at least openly).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;thoughts&quot;&gt;Thoughts&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;david-burns-warped-thoughts&quot;&gt;David Burns’ Warped Thoughts&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;All or None Thinking.&lt;/strong&gt; Everything is perceived to be either full on or full off.  If something isn’t fully completed, right, or perfect then it’s entirely incomplete/wrong/spoiled.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Overgeneralization.&lt;/strong&gt; One instance of a mistake/error is interpreted as a pattern of mistakes/errors (as if it’s gonna happen always).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mental Filter.&lt;/strong&gt; The small (negative) part of the picture is examined to the exclusion of the larger (positive) part.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Denying the Positive.&lt;/strong&gt; Dismissing the positive remark/compliment given to you.  (e.g., My brother said he looked up to me… but what does he know… he’s just a kid.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jumping to Conclusions.&lt;/strong&gt; You think about what others would say (mind reading) or you think about what will happen in the future (fortune telling) without any evidence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2014 07:43:58 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>www.anton23.com/life/2014/09/11/cognitive-behavior-therapy/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">www.anton23.com/life/2014/09/11/cognitive-behavior-therapy/</guid>
        
        
        <category>life</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Voice</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’d like to think that the voice has some calming effects.  In some ways, it should be considered as a mutant power (I’m a super-hero fanboy after all).  Hence, today I set out to find exercises that would help me improve the way I project my voice.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Resonate your voice through your chest.&lt;/strong&gt;  Science has said time and time again that a deeper voice in men is correlated to positive attributes.  The only way to deepen the voice is if one is talking through the chest as opposed thru the throat or nose, and if one coordinates breathing accordingly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Enunciate and pronounce the words correctly.&lt;/strong&gt;  Can you even hear yourself (volume)?  Are you talking thru each syllable you just uttered (tempo/speed)?  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Pause accordingly.&lt;/strong&gt; Stop using sounds/words as a crutch (e.g., ummm…, so…) to continuously talk.  Have you start creating any dramatic effect with your pauses?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most of your power as a man is conveyed through your bodylanguage and the way you speak. In this post I want to spend a few words on the way you speak, just some basics to get the ball rolling. You don’t have to sound like Barry White and you don’t have to sound like a robot intoning every syllable, but certain principles hold: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Enunciate clearly and slowly — slow the fuck down when you speak—most people speak too fast. Fast speaking stems from a fear that your input is worthless and it bespeaks insecurity and sounds unnnnsexy (even in women, over-fast speaking looks anxious and nervy). There’s nothing as annoying as a mumbling person you can’t understand or you have to struggle to understand, so speak up. Project your voice, make it heard. Tyler Durden aka Owen Cook doesn’t have a deep voice at all but he’s excellent at projecting his voice.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Don’t trail off or end sentences with “so”, or end your sentences with uptalk (aka a rising inflection) as though you’re maybe asking a question? It’s you know, very beta? Speak like a fuckin man maybe, like?&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Violently excise all lip smacking shit and weird tics like swallowing while talking; it’s immensely annoying.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Reduce verbal filler, like uhh, uhmm, like, yaknow. Silence is better while you gather your thoughts, as long as it doesn’t stretch on too long. In general don’t worry about the silences (Ironically, it’s when you blather that people are less likely to listen to and value your words.)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Don’t let people cut you off and talk over you when you’re making a point. Finish your sentence.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;In public speaking use moderate tones. Low talkers (edit: speaking too quietly) and shouters don’t sound confident, and they’re annoying.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Using vivid metaphors and imagery is a secret to making your words memorable, even captivating. You may not have realised why, but the most boring speakers are speakers who rarely use metaphors and whose words are steeped in fuzzy abstractions.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Listen well. It’s immensely charming when someone shows a genuine interest in the other person - there’s a skill to this, which is hard to convey in writing, but the essence of it is: don’t appear to be trying to listen too hard with some ulterior motive. Sincere interest in another person and asking them questions, and not just waiting to speak - this is like psychologically stroking someone. Caveat: tone it town for spastic and hot attention whores.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;This last one is important: Don’t be verbally incontinent. Laconicism is sexier than stream of consciousness blathering. Verbosity is womanly, especially self-absorbed verbosity. Doesn’t mean you have to be Clint Eastwood, but unless your personality is fruity and high energy then make your words count, make your input to the group conversation valuable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2014 07:43:58 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>www.anton23.com/life/exercise/interact/2014/08/27/the-voice/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">www.anton23.com/life/exercise/interact/2014/08/27/the-voice/</guid>
        
        
        <category>life</category>
        
        <category>exercise</category>
        
        <category>interact</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Poem for Rob</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/y4xXSQ1.png&quot; alt=&quot;Alt text&quot; title=&quot;Image Unit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This week is my former boss’s last week at Lucasfilm, and those of use who were close 
to him were asked to create a going away note which will be presented to him on his final day.
I ended up being more creative than I thought.  I originally intended to just create a poem.  After
everything’s been done, an awesome backdrop has been made along with the poem using GIMP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Farewell, Rob!  T’was a ride.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;o-captain-my-captain&quot;&gt;O Captain! My Captain!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;O Captain! My Captain! Our fearful trip is done;&lt;br /&gt;
The ship has weather’d every rack, the prize we sought is won;&lt;br /&gt;
The port is near, the bells I hear, the people all exulting,&lt;br /&gt;
While follow eyes the steady keel, the vessel grim and daring.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;O Captain! My Captain! You sailed the ship to the beat of its drum;&lt;br /&gt;
One by one your men has gone, and now your time has come.&lt;br /&gt;
Through triumphs, through turmoil, and all else in between, 
All we can say is “Thank You.” What a journey it has been!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;O Captain! My Captain! Farewell to thee…&lt;br /&gt;
In your new voyage I know you’ll be set free.&lt;br /&gt;
‘Tis time for a new adventure, a new ship, and a new crew.&lt;br /&gt;
Make us proud, make it true, may your focus be you.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2014 07:43:58 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>www.anton23.com/poems/2014/08/26/a-poem-for-rob/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">www.anton23.com/poems/2014/08/26/a-poem-for-rob/</guid>
        
        
        <category>poems</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Creating Improv Masters</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;pick-the-color-scheme&quot;&gt;Pick the Color Scheme…&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Orange is the color of Energy, Happiness, and Vitality.  These qualities embody 
improv, so this will be the main color of the Improv Masters site. And what goes well with
orange? It’s complementary blue, of course.  Hence, here’s the scheme:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/EuAL9Mh.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;typography&quot;&gt;Typography&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since improv is within arts and culture, the type will be in Modern Serif Fonts.
&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/s5R8WUM.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;font&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;-&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;ss&quot;&gt;family&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;Didot&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;err&quot;&gt;“&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;Didot&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;LT&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;STD&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;err&quot;&gt;”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;err&quot;&gt;“&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;Hoefler&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;Text&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;err&quot;&gt;”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;Garamond&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;err&quot;&gt;“&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;Times&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;New&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;Roman&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;err&quot;&gt;”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;serif&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2014 07:43:58 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>www.anton23.com/skills/2014/07/28/creating-improv-masters/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">www.anton23.com/skills/2014/07/28/creating-improv-masters/</guid>
        
        
        <category>skills</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Design: Layout</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;visual-hierarchy&quot;&gt;Visual Hierarchy&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Arrange elements to engage and direct the users eye.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;English is read from left to right, so start from the upper-left corner especially with logo/brand.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Next is navigation.
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Few items – Horizontal (top bar) or Vertical (side bar) works well.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Many items – Vertical excels.  Horizontal works if it’s a tiered system.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Dropdowns/Flyouts – works well in both systems.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Vertical navigation is not used that much&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Main Content – content should reinforce the hierarchy
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Make sure all directional cues are pointing to the content.
        &lt;ul&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;e.g., Use images of people that look towards the content (see image below).&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Secondary Content – should be smaller and relegated to the side or underneath the main content.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Footer – bottom of the page and provides quick hint information for users. 
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;It should always span the width of the page.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/zZesJtv.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/9BaPcDn.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-grid-system&quot;&gt;The Grid System&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;It is made up of vertical lines that create columns with gutters in-between them.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;It also has horizontal lines that create a baseline for text that is equal to the line-height.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Always respect the gutters&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/yoArX79.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;fixed-vs-fluid&quot;&gt;Fixed vs Fluid&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fixed grid has constant width.  A fluid grid grows and shrinks with the browser window.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;incorporate-whitespace&quot;&gt;Incorporate Whitespace&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ample empty space around elements can increase readability and create a mood of elegance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Even in images, there’s white space that’s surrounding the subject.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Density is lack of whitespace.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;balance-all-the-things&quot;&gt;Balance all the things&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A good design is a balanced design.  It can be symmetrical or asymmetrical.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Symmetry – portrays a sense of stabilty and trust.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Asymmetry – effective in drawing attention and breaking monotony.  It is inherently balanced, and creates intrigue and demands attention.  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/gmGesNH.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;all-of-the-principles-together-contribute-to-balance&quot;&gt;All of the principles together Contribute to Balance.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Size, Color, Contribute, Alignment (grid), Whitespace (or lack thereof–density) and Symmetry create balance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;final-notes&quot;&gt;Final Notes:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;If you can’t defend it, Change It
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Design with intentionality, the ability to defend your design decisions in a conversational manner. If you can’t defend it, its probably not the right choice.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Experiment Often
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;The first solution is rarely the best one, don’t rush the process.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2014 07:43:58 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>www.anton23.com/skills/2014/07/12/design-layout/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">www.anton23.com/skills/2014/07/12/design-layout/</guid>
        
        
        <category>skills</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Design: Color</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;color-theory-101&quot;&gt;Color Theory 101:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are 2 types of color: color you can touch (subtractive color)
and color you can’t touch (additive color).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Subtractive Color – CMYK&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Additive Color – RGB&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;hsl&quot;&gt;HSL&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Humans process color in Hue, Saturation, Lightness.  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Most applications refer to Lightness as Brightness where the maximum value is 
the most vibrant color.  (Lightness’s maximum value is white.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;color-scheme&quot;&gt;Color Scheme&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s a collection of 4-5 colors built into the style guide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/81q88zc.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Steps in Building a Color Scheme:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Start by selecting a base color – different colors create different moods.
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;red – heat, passion, excitement. Easily grabs a)ention and evokes speed and energy.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;orange – warmth, vitality.  Associated with reliability &amp;amp; playfulness.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;yellow – optimism, creativity.  Represents sunshine, cheer, and happiness.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;green – serenity, health.  Connotes growth, nature, freshness.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;blue – security, truth, stability. Implies loyalty, reliability and an open communication&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;purple – spirituality, intelligence, wealth.  Also means royal, sentimental, and sophisticated.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;pink – youthful intensity.  Conveys energy, fun and excitement.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;brown – durability, class. Represents age, stabili$ and relaxation.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;black – power, drama. It’s serious, bold and strong.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;white – simplicity, cleanliness.  It’s message is youthful, mild and pure.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Keep culture in mind when choosing a base color.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Build Scheme around base color.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/NM1JoMf.png&quot; alt=&quot;w500&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/qsGyiAG.png&quot; alt=&quot;w500&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/RepXI6G.png&quot; alt=&quot;w500&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;color--type&quot;&gt;Color &amp;amp; type&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Contrast is the difference in colors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Contrast of Hue&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Contrast of Saturation&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Contrast of Lightness&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;most-contrasts-are-multi-faceted&quot;&gt;Most contrasts are multi-faceted.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s common to combine contrasts of Hue,
Saturation, or Brightness. The left part of the image below shows a contrast of 
Hue only; the right part shows a contrast of Hue &amp;amp; Brightness. WCAG determines the the standard for contrasts.  It stands for Web Content 
Accessibility Guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/gMRWgSh.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;High-contrast colors are the best (e.g., black and white)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Same Hue, but high saturation &amp;amp; brightness contrast are second. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some contrasts are intrinsically difficult for humans to distinguish (and 
are plain ugly too).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/QmBHemf.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;natural-values&quot;&gt;Natural Values&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Different colors have different natural values.  For example, yellow is a 
naturally light color and blue is naturally dark.  Creating contrast where
yellow is darker than the blue creates an awkward user-experience.  However,
this can be fixed by adjusting the lightness to make yellow be lighter and blue 
darker – so as to correspond with the natural values.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/9SAMo1W.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;warm--cold-colors&quot;&gt;Warm &amp;amp; Cold Colors&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Red, orange, &amp;amp; yellow side are warm.  Green, blue, and purple are on the cooler side.
Use warm &amp;amp; cold to create depth.  Warm is always closer, and cold is in the back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/GdjR4nf.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/jpd33E4.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;visual-hierarchy&quot;&gt;Visual Hierarchy&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Combine colors to reinforce a hierarchy.  Use color differences to contribute 
to relationships between elements on the page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/XqQ2sZF.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;types-and-images&quot;&gt;Types and Images&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Don’t be tacky – Don’t add effects (dropshadows, strokes, etc.) on text.
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Instead, treat the image (overlay, darken, etc.) on the background to make the text stand out.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Type in an image – Dont do it! Professional copy doesn’t belong in an image.
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;(Unless it’s cat meme, or a blog post for personal use ;-) )&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Below is a good example of color combination that was used on Code School’s site.
A combination of analogous, complementary colors with high enough contrast for 
text colors and backgrounds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/UN2it1x.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2014 07:43:58 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>www.anton23.com/skills/2014/07/11/design-color/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">www.anton23.com/skills/2014/07/11/design-color/</guid>
        
        
        <category>skills</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Design: Typography</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;style-guide&quot;&gt;Style Guide&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reference document for multiple instances of typography/styles that would 
be used throughout your application.  An example is shown below.  Putting this
guide beforehand will avoid any inconsistency and create a better overall 
design/user-experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/ZLXQtur.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;typography-is-both-visual-and-verbal&quot;&gt;Typography is both Visual and Verbal&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Different classifications of type create different moods that will either
server your content well or not. The reader surveys the overall graphical 
patterns of the page, and then parse the language and read.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;History… A basic system for classifying typefaces was devised in the nineteenth century, when printers sought to identify a heritage for their own craft analogous to that of art history. &lt;em&gt;Humanist&lt;/em&gt; letterforms are closely connected to calligraphy and the movement of the hand. &lt;em&gt;Transitional&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;modern&lt;/em&gt; typefaces are more abstract and less organic. These three main groups correspond roughly to the Renaissance, Baroque, and Enlightenment periods in art and literature. Designers in the twentieth and twenty-first centuries have continued to create new typefaces based on historic characteristics. &lt;a href=&quot;http://papress.com/thinkingwithtype/letter/classification.htm&quot;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Below are the most common classification of types…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;serif-font&quot;&gt;Serif Font&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Serifs are the small lines tailing from the edges of letters. Some styles of 
type in this Serif Classification are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Humanist – great for historical or journalism applications&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Transitional – traditional academia and legal&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Modern – arts and culture&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Egyptian – marketing and promotional&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/Zs5zo2S.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/y2oLzyq.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/vF8inNJ.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/xYv4Sbh.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;sans-serif-font&quot;&gt;Sans Serif Font&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Humanist Sans – government or education&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Transitional Sans – technology or transportation&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Geometric Sans – science or architecture&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/ZbM9mpq.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/LhxJsqI.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/MzJ38Os.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;script-font&quot;&gt;Script Font&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Good for adding human element to the site, but not so great for body copy.
Comic sans is technically a script font.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;mix--mingle&quot;&gt;Mix &amp;amp; Mingle&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Don’t choose two fonts from the same style (e.g., humanist serif &amp;amp; humanist serif)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Don’t choose two fonts from the same style (e.g., humanist serif &amp;amp; slan serif)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;When mixing classes find a similar trait (e.g., humanist serif &amp;amp; humanist sans)
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;this trait can even be largely abstract&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Strive for &lt;strong&gt;Contrast over Harmony&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;A good rule of thumb to follow is “Keep it the same or 
change it a lot. Look for emphatic differences rather than mushy transitions.”&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Single Typeface is Okay – never feel obligated to use two.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;font-size&quot;&gt;Font Size&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Humans create relationships.  It’s how our brain processes. 
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;bigger items that stand out appear to be more important.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;the headline in big/bold fonts indicate the main topic of an article.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;a pic of red bell pepper on a site indicates food theme&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;a sea of text becomes on a site becomes troublesome for the audience 
because it’s hard to &lt;strong&gt;assess&lt;/strong&gt; what the site is about right away.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;So create a visual hierarchy!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;when-creating-a-style-guide&quot;&gt;When creating a style guide…&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Set the Body Copy first – this is usually around 16px (convert to ems or rems when necessary).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Headline Text – around 200% to 300% of the body copy.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;B-head (or sub-head) Text – around 150% of the body copy.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Navigational Text – same size as body copy.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Byline Text – around 75% of the body copy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;leading&quot;&gt;Leading&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Leading is the amount of space between lines of text.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Leading that is too large negatively affects readability and produces discontinuity&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Leading that is too tight creates a claustrophobic feel&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Good leading is around 120% to 150% of the body copy size.
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;setting &lt;code&gt;line-height: 1.5&lt;/code&gt; provides 150% the font’s size.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;bold--italics&quot;&gt;Bold &amp;amp; Italics&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Use a “less is more” approach.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Use natural convention – e.g., eyes naturally expect headlines to be in bold rather than body copy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;line-width&quot;&gt;Line Width&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Lines that are too short are difficult to read as the user’s eyes have to jump 
quickly from line to line.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Lines that are too long can get the user’s eyes lost easily.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;characters-per-line&quot;&gt;Characters per Line&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Line width is measured in CPL (characters per line)
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;50 - 70 CPL is ideal (including spaces)&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;In CSS, CPL can be adjusted using &lt;code&gt;max-width&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;save-the-orphans-and-widows&quot;&gt;Save the Orphans and Widows&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They impede the natural flow of reading for the user.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A widow is a single word on a line of text&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;An orphan is a single line of text on a column/page&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2014 07:43:59 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>www.anton23.com/skills/2014/07/10/design-typography/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">www.anton23.com/skills/2014/07/10/design-typography/</guid>
        
        
        <category>skills</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
